让震荡波在这艘飞船上整出一支野兽大军
Is it really wise for Shockwave to spawn an army of beasts
凭这狭小的实验室 似乎不太明智吧
here in this laboratory, or within any part of this warship?
我是说 光是以前的那只 飞船就已经容不下了
I mean, not even the lone beast we had was compact enough
它在走廊里闲逛几乎能把墙给拆了
to stroll these corridors without tearing them asunder.
说到它 你可要节哀啊
Which reminds me, I am so very sorry for your loss.
我将使用我的外部实验室
I was referring to my offsite laboratory
那是我特地为这项克隆程序准备的
which we have erected expressly for the cloning procedures.
就没有你考虑不到的 是吧？
You think of everything, don't you?
我们遭到了攻击
We are under attack.
汽车人？
Autobots?
不合逻辑
Illogical.
但我确实在飞船顶部探测到一个体型巨大的物体
Though there appears to be an enormous mass upon the upper hull.
它是怎么找到我们的？
How did it find us?
巨狰狞有精确的归巢本能
Predacons possess precise homing instincts.
以及惊人的生存能力
And astonishing resilience.
红蜘蛛 这只巨狰狞交给你指挥了
Starscream, assume command of my beast.
我？主人？
Me, master?
我是说 我怎好意思从它的创造者那里夺走这份殊荣呢？
I... I mean, I wouldn't dream of seizing such an honor from its very creator.
将巨狰狞交由军事部门管辖是符合逻辑的
Military command of the Predacon is most logical
鉴于我将全身心投入研究领域
since my services are required elsewhere.
好了 野兽猎人们 根据情报
All right, Beast Hunters. According to our intel
霸天虎将在正下方位置挖掘巨狰狞的骸骨
the Decepticons should be excavating for Predacon bones directly beneath us.
我上了 头儿
On it, chief.
难道千斤顶就不会等待上级的命令么
Does Wheeljack not comprehend the chain of command?
我并未许可他在没有掩护的情况下只身冒进
I didn't authorize him to advance without proper cover.
呃…我想老千只是想当着您的面 证明一下他自己 长官
Yeah... I'm sure Jackie's just trying to prove himself now that you and he are serving together again, sir.
依－哈！
Yee-ha!
老千 等一下
Jackie, wait up.
通天晓要我们…
Ultra Magnus wants us...
这个…介个…那个…
Blah, blah, blah.
嘘！嘘！
Shh! Shh!
雷霆救援队的第17条真理：
Wrecker fact number 17:
守卫从不抬头看上面
"Guards never look up."
糟了
Scrap.
这就是为什么得有人来掩护
That's why we wait for cover.
唉 真不是时候
Ah, bolts.
嗯…
Uh...
把你给忘了 小鬼
Forgot you were in there, kid.
至少这次没让我待在脚垫儿上
At least I didn't heave on any floormats this time.
你这只悲催的野兽 我是你的指挥官
You miserable beast. I am your commanding officer
我命令你立刻爬回你的窝里去
and I order you to crawl into your kennel, now!
我说了 快去！
I said go, already!
啊！
Ahh!
你到底有什么不可抗拒的理由 非要把这个人类带来？
And what could have possibly compelled you to bring the nativ?
嘿
Yo.
我能一起去吗？
Can I come with?
没问题
Why not?
你是不是头脑短路了 士兵？
Are your circuits impaired, soldier?
擎天柱派你带领雷霆救援队执行这次任务
Prime told you to lead the Wreckers on this one.
我觉得他是指所有队员
I assumed he meant all of 'em.
你是在跟你的上级开玩笑么？
Are you mocking your commanding officer?
哪敢呢 长官
Wouldn't think of it, sir.
这孩子能耐大着呢 对不对 隔板？
The kid's a full-blown Wrecker. Isn't that right, Bulkhead?
这个嘛…
Well...
听着 或许她个头不大 但她救过我的命
Look. She may be small, but she saved my tailpipe.
她独自干掉了一只机器昆虫
Snuffed an Insecticon all on her own.
毫无疑问 一定又没遵守章程
Outside standard protocol, no doubt.
关键是 我能照顾好自己 长官
The point is, I can handle myself, sir.
神子经历过更严峻的考验
Miko has been through worse
而且我们已经引出了敌人 通道也清理干净了
and we've drawn out the enemy and cleared passage.
好了 现在你给我进去
Okay, now in you go.
来咬我啊 这精锐护甲可不是…
Do your worst. The Apex armor is virtually...
啊！啊！噢！不！啊！放开我！
Ahh! Oh, oh! No! Ahh! Release me!
红蜘蛛 那只野兽在你那里吗？
Starscream, are you with the beast?
是的 主人
Yes, master.
我们正在进行攻击练习呢 他表现良好
We've been reviewing attack maneuvers. He's doing quite well.
一支挖掘小队和我们失去了联系
One of the excavation teams has failed to report in.
我立刻召集我的追踪者大军…
I shall assemble my seeker armada immediately and...
我希望你带领我们失而复得的资产去执行这个任务
I would prefer that you lead our newly-returned asset on this mission
这样我们可以看看巨狰狞\N搜寻骸骨的能力是不是和猎杀汽车人一样出色
so that we may see if our Predacon is as adept at fetching bones as it is hunting Autobots.
是它吗？
Is this it?
不 那是块石头
No. That is a rock.
哈 重温旧日时光啊 老千
Heh. Just like old times, huh, Jackie?
以前我选择队友可不需要别人批准
Except back then, I didn't need permission to pick my partners.
行了 我们是一伙的
Come on, we're all on the same team.
嘿 我们都是野兽猎人嘛 对吧？
Hey, Beast Hunters, right?
到达地球之前 当我在宇宙中徘徊时
During all those cycles it took me to travel to Earth
我满脑子想的都是重聚我们失散的战友
all I could think about was getting our band of brothers back together.
不过我可从没把他算上
But this isn't the lineup I had in mind.
你当时离开雷霆救援队 真是明智
You did the smart thin, Bulk, leaving the Wreckers when you did.
那时候我们才算得上真正的利刃 在被某人带成钝刀之前
While we were still bringing our A-game, before the rust set in.
等等 我以为是千斤顶离开了雷霆救援队
Wait, I thought Wheeljack was the one who left the Wreckers.
当通天晓接手雷霆救援队时 老千基本上被遗弃了
Jackie basically deserted once the Wreckers fell under Ultra Magnus' command.
我在那之前就被调到了擎天柱的队伍 参加了雷云关之战
I transferred out before that, to join up with Optimus in the battle of Thunderhead Pass.
有时候我感觉 老千认为我抛弃了他
Sometimes I think Jackie feels like I deserted him.
你不是那种抛弃战友的人 小隔
You don't wanna be the one who breaks up the band, Bulk.
噢！
Oh!
怎么回事？
What was that?
不管那是什么 它的个头可不小
Whatever it is, it's big.
而且速度也不慢
And it's coming fast.
巨狰狞 我们走！
The Predacon. Let's roll.
它回来了？
It's back?
加速！
Accelerate!
那些石头挡不住它多久 必须联系基地以请求支援
That rock won't hold it forever. We need to contact base and request reinforcements.
雷霆救援队从不请求支援
Wreckers don't call for backup.
老千的意思是说 这里距离地表太远 没有通讯信号
What Jackie means is, we can't get a comm-link signal this far underground.
神子 我得把你弄出去 你得从这儿爬上去
Miko, I have to get you out of here. Gonna need you to climb.
没门儿 我要帮忙
No way. I wanna help.
我同意
And you will.
你的任务是：回到我的飞船 然后联系擎天柱
Your mission: Reach my ship so you can contact Optimus Prime.
遵命 长官！
Yes, sir.
听起来 情况可不太妙
Not sure I like the sound of that.
那么…
So, uh...
我们拼死一搏 就在此时此地！
We make our stand... here and now.
鉴于飞船内空无一人
Given that this ship is currently unoccupied
看来汽车人又在我们的挖掘行动中插了一脚
it would seem the Autobots did stumble upon our little mining operation.
不过别担心
No worries.
“我的”巨狰狞此时一定\N正在把那些碍眼的家伙大卸八块呢
My Predacon is no doubt dismantling the interlopers as we speak.
要驯服那家伙确实不简单 不过这还是难不倒我
It was a challenge, but I managed to tame the savage beast.
现在它已经对我言听计从了
Taught it to heed my every command.
快走开 快走开
Come on, come on.
这么说 你穿这身行头不是怕它咬你？
You're not wearing the armor to protect yourself from it?
怕我可爱的狞狞？怎么可能呢
From my beloved pet? Of course not.
说实在的 穿这个还真是有点热呢
In fact, it's getting rather warm in here.
哈 清爽透气了
Ah, ventilation.
开火！
Open fire!
哇哦！
Whoa!
想都别想！
No you don't.
嘿 火焰山！
Hey, hot-head!
这下惨了
Oh, scrap.
噢 这肯定够他们受的
Ooh, that'll do some damage.
你叫神子 对吧？
Miko, is it?
噢 不好意思
Oh, I'm sorry.
或许你是想用这艘飞船呼叫支援吧？
Were you trying to reach this ship? To call for help, perhaps?
怎么了 小红？欺软怕硬惯了？
What's the matter, 'Screamy? Can't pick on someone your own size?
没想到 它还真找到了
What do you know, it does fetch.
糟了
Scrap.
好吧 剧本没有如期上演
Well, that didn't go exacty as planned.
就连入伍只有一周期的新兵都知道\N不能在一个封闭的空间引爆手雷
That's because any first-cycle Cadet knows better than to detonate a grenade in a confined space.
即使把那只野兽的肚子当成“封闭的空间”也不行么？
Even if I intended the "confined space" to be the belly of the beast?
嗯…长官
Uh, sir...
你的鲁莽行为差一点害死我们所有人
Your actions continue to be just one step removed from getting us all scrapped.
我无意冒犯 长官
With all due respect, sir
但巨狰狞已经逃脱 而神子在外孤身一人
the Predacon's loose and Miko's out there alone.
允许我去提供掩护么 长官？
Permission to provide cover, sir?
继续 撕了她 就像你在下面对雷霆救援队所做的
Go ahead, make a wreck of her, as you no doubt did the Wreckers.
红蜘蛛 报告情况
Starscream, status report.
主人 我们已经取得了骨骸 而巨狰狞此刻正在处理汽车人的人类宠物
Master. We have secured the bone, and our Predacon is dealing with the Autobots' pet human as we speak.
当然 是在我的指挥下
On my command, of course.
我不会冒险让珍贵的骨骸因你的自大而丢失
I will not risk losing a precious commodity to your arrogance.
我要拆了你！
I'll tear you apart!
立刻让巨狰狞带着我的战利品返回基地！
Have the beast return with my prize, immediately!
你留下解决那些汽车人
You can stay behind and finish the Autobots.
遵命 主人
Yes, master.
不知道能不能让这头愚蠢的野兽…
Assuming I can coerce the brainless brute into...
什么？你怎么从来不听我的命令！
But, you never obey my commands!
你们都听到主人的命令了 我们必须立刻找到那些汽车人
You heard our Master. We must locate the Autobots.
不过我先要拿回属于我的东西
As soon as I retrieve what belongs to me.
啧啧啧 即使最强大的护甲也无法保护最弱小的生物
Tsk, tsk, tsk, tsk... Even the strongest armor can't protect the weakest of creatures.
它不是保护过你么？
Protected you, didn't it?
现在 看看到底谁拆谁？
Who's wrecking who now?
神子？
Miko?
或许你对这个人类的评价并没有错
Perhaps you weren't wrong about the human after all.
你知道是我干掉了飞过山吧？
You do know that I vanquished Cliffjumper, don't you?
别显摆了
Big whoop.
我干掉过硬壳！
I snuffed Hardshell.
啊！撤退
Ah! Retreat.
啊！
Aw.
他们把骸骨带走了
They got away with the bone.
嘿 你的表现非常出色 小鬼
Hey, you brought your A-game, kid
无愧于雷霆救援队的称号
like a true Wrecker.
我要记住你们现在的样子
And I wanna remember us just like this...
趁着某人还没把你们变成钝刀
before the rust sets in.
怎么？千斤顶要去哪儿？
What? Where's Wheeljack going?
单飞
Solo.
又一次？
Again?
老千把我们的乐队解散了
Jackie just broke up the band.